(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Recipe share is a full-stack web application
designed for users to share, save and get
personalized recommendations on recipes and also to explore
recipes and chefs worldwide.
Now let's move to recipes tab.
Recipes section consists of recommended for you recipes
and all recipes.
All recipes consist of all the recipes data
from the database.
We can filter it based on cuisine type,
labels and maximum cooking time.
Let's explore one individual recipe.
We can now like the recipe, save the
recipe and also share the recipe.
Let's listen to the audio.
Let's now explore recommended for you section.
Recommended for you section uses ml power recommendation
system to recommend to users.
It uses three different type of ml models
for recommending.
First one is the most powerful two-tower
neural network architecture such as in this system.
It uses two different towers such as user
and recipe embeddings and calculates similarity between these
two and recommends similar recipes to the users.
Second one is alternative least squares method.
This method computes nested factorization between user to
item embeddings and recommends similar items to the
users.
Third one is popularity-based method.
This method simply recommends popular recipes and popular
shapes to the users directly.
This is the feed section.
Your users can explore feed and also post
their updates directly with images.
Here is the discover tab and your user
can discover top trending recipes and chefs.
Here is the chefs tab.
Your user can discover all of the chefs
and also get personalized recommendation of chefs.
User can also follow other chefs and also
they can filter out chefs based on most
recipes or most followers.
The recommended for you chefs that is the
personalized recommendation for user works similar to that
of recommended for recipes section.
Here is the notification where user get notification
and here is the messages page where user
can message to their specific mutual connections.
This is the specific user profile page where
the individual user can delete their recipes, manage
their recipes and also view their recipes as
well.
This is the search bar in our website
where user can search for specific item recipes
or cuisine types.
The users can also create a new recipe.
They can fill in this information, can also
upload an image and then submit the recipe.
After submitting the recipe, the new recipe will
appear in their profile page such as this
ice cake.